export default data = [
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 1,
    num1: 24,
    num2: 10,
    operator: '+',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 1,
    num1: 59,
    num2: 7,
    operator: '-',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 1,
    num1: 109,
    num2: 1,
    operator: '+',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 1,
    num1: 47,
    num2: 8,
    operator: '-',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 2,
    num1: 105,
    num2: 58,
    operator: '+',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 2,
    num1: 3,
    num2: 7,
    operator: '*',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 2,
    num1: 13,
    num2: 2,
    operator: '*',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 2,
    num1: 285,
    num2: 18,
    operator: '-',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 3,
    num1: 24,
    num2: 9,
    operator: '*',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 3,
    num1: 1379,
    num2: 556,
    operator: '+',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 3,
    num1: 268,
    num2: 552,
    operator: '-',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 3,
    num1: 148,
    num2: 4,
    operator: '/',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 4,
    num1: 1673,
    num2: 326,
    operator: '-',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 4,
    num1: 284,
    num2: 12,
    operator: '*',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 4,
    num1: 7,
    num2: 1596,
    operator: '*',
  },
  {
    type: 'Login',
    level: 4,
    num1: 3612,
    num2: 3,
    operator: '/',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 1,
    question: 'Jenny _______ the soccer match.',
    choices: ['watches', 'watched', 'watch'],
    answer: 'watches',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 1,
    question: 'Jim is not as strong as James and ___.',
    choices: ['I', 'me'],
    answer: 'me',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 1,
    question: 'I like to _____ down hills.',
    choices: ['ran', 'run', 'running'],
    answer: 'run',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 1,
    question: 'My teacher is the ______!',
    choices: ['bestest', 'awesomest', 'greatest'],
    answer: 'greatest',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 2,
    question: 'Mark the correct spelling of the word:',
    choices: ['appul', 'appil', 'appole', 'apple'],
    answer: 'apple',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    question: 'The dog sprints away ______.',
    choices: ['fast', 'fastly', 'quick', 'quickly'],
    answer: 'quickly',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    question: 'My friend Bob took my soda. Bob is a _________.',
    choices: ['trader', 'traitor', 'carpenter', 'psychopath'],
    answer: 'traitor',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 2,
    question: '_________: to move or go in a stealthy manner.',
    choices: ['Sneak', 'Plod', 'Trot', 'Consume'],
    answer: 'Sneak',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 3,
    question: 'I enjoy taking a bus, riding a horse, and I fly on airplanes. This sentence has issues with:',
    choices: ['Spelling', 'Capitalization', 'Parallel Structure', 'Comma Usage'],
    answer: 'Parallel Structure',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 3,
    question: 'A word that describes a person, place, or thing.',
    choices: ['verb', 'adjective', 'adverb', 'noun'],
    answer: 'adjective',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 3,
    question: 'James only left the room for a moment, but I noticed *his* abscence. *His* refers to:',
    choices: ['James', 'the writer', 'the reader'],
    answer: 'James',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 3,
    question: '"Take a _______ he said, "you overwork yourself too often."',
    choices: ['break"', 'break', 'break",', 'break,"'],
    answer: 'break,"',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 4,
    question: "I've been in quite a few _________, and this is the nicest.",
    choices: ["cottages'", "cottage", "cottages", "cottage's"],
    answer: 'cottages',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 4,
    question: 'True or false: Subjects have to come before verbs.',
    choices: ['true', 'false'],
    answer: 'false',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 4,
    question: "Jessica's dress flowed off her shoulders with a(n) *eloquence* none of her peers could match.",
    choices: ['No change', 'extravagance', 'shape', 'exuberance'],
    answer: 'No change',
  },
  {
    type: 'Signup',
    level: 4,
    question: "Gillian's potato farm is in peril this year. The government has banned *pesticides; which* is a problem for Gillian.",
    choices: ['No change', 'pesticides. Which', 'pesticides, which', 'pesticides which'],
    answer: 'pesticides, which',
  },
]